异 种
三十年来 一直有射电望远镜观察宇宙
寻找外星文化的讯号
这项计划是S.E.T.I.
探索地外生命计划
犹他州德威市　美国政府实验室
氰化物毒气
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起？
I'm sorry?
长官 她逃出来了
Sir, she's breaking out!
我们在找什么？
What are we looking for?
她跳过了围栏
She jumped over the fence!
她逃走时有数辆火车经过
A couple of trains came through here about the time she escaped.
你认为在那段时间内她能跑到这么远吗？
Do you think she could have gotten this far in that time?
她能跑那么快吗？
Is she that fast?
她就是这样快
She is that fast.
还有这个
And this too.
- 三元一角 - 三元一角？
- $3. 10. - Three dollars and ten cents?
- 你的零钱 - 谢谢
- Your change. - Thank you.
有什么可以帮你？
Can I help you?
总共17.95元
The total is $ 17.95.
你的卡
Here's your card.
你要买下全部吗？
Are you gonna buy those?
那是咖啡色花纹
Have a nice trip.
像运动袋的 你有看到吗？
It's brown tweed bag, like a duffel. Do you see it anywhere?
- 先生 这儿没有 - 服务生说把它放在手推车上
- Sir, it's not here. - The porter said he put it on the cart.
这是手推车 但上面没有运动袋
This is the cart. There's no bag here.
当局说这是有史以来最严重的地震
Government authorities said it was the largest earthquake to strike...
他骑上了油脂闪光
He's riding Greased Lightning.
那是矮子加特
That was Shorty Kincaid.
欣赏风景
Enjoy the view.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我们不该被人看见走在一起
We shouldn 't be seen together.
爸爸刚去世不久 你觉得艾伦有怀疑吗？
Father hasn 't been dead long. Do you think Arlen suspects?
不 对我们在一起来说 还不算太快
No. It's not too soon for us to be together.
你的车票
Tickets.
你单独旅行吗？
Are you traveling by yourself?
你是十二岁？
You're 12?
在洛杉矶有人来接你吗？
Someone meeting you in Los Angeles?
我们会说你是十一岁 那你便会有半价优惠
We'll say you're 11. Then you only pay half price.
我们的小女孩干的吗？
Our little girl did this?
她不是小女孩
She's not a little girl.
在伤口找到的DNA证实是她
DNA typing and material found in those wounds proves it was her.
她可能到了任何地方 芝加哥 拉斯维加斯和洛杉矶
She could be anywhere. Chicago, Las Vegas, Los Angeles, anywhere.
我们该截停那些火车
We should stop the trains.
但我们能回答铁路局和警察的问题吗？
And have the railroad and police ask questions we can't answer?
我们要在铁路沿线的每个车站派人驻守
We'll put key personnel at every stop along these lines.
派一队人追踪她
I want a team to track her.
一定要找到她
Hunt her down.
- 吉尔 早晨 - 哈啰
- Good morning, Jill. - Hello.
- 感谢你替我照顾猫儿 - 我们会好好照顾他
- Thanks for taking care of my cat. - We'll take good care of him.
我不会离开很久
I won't be gone very long.
保重
Take care.
再见
Bye-bye.
你在工作上还有问题吗？
Are you still having problems with the people at work?
他们指着我…
They point their finger at me saying...
说我是怪诞的人 说我很奇怪
I'm the weird one, I'm the strange one.
为什么？因为我有感觉吗？
Why? Because I have feelings?
因为我有感应吗？
Because I feel?
门外有人
There's someone at the door.
不必理会 不管是谁 一小时后他会再来
I won't answer that. Whoever it is can come back at the end of the hour.
这是找我的
That's for me.
抱歉打扰你们 丹 我们需要你帮忙
Sorry to interrupt. We need your help, Dan.
我知道
I know.
走吧
Gotta go.
稍后费舒先生会来见你们
Mr. Fitch will be with you all in just a moment.
这样…
Well...
我们来这里的原因应是相同的
I guess we all must be here for the same reason...
不管原因是什么
whatever that is.
我是史丹
I'm Dan Smithson...
我不知道为何会来这里
and I don't know why I'm here either.
但是… 他们说是重要的事需要我帮忙 所以我来了
But they said they needed me and it was important, so I came.
你干什么的？
What do you do, Dan?
我是心灵感应者
I'm an empath.
有时他们让我看人们做过的可怕事
Sometimes they show me awful things people have done.
我尝试给他们解释原因
I try to tell them why they did it.
你有何资格做这种工作？
What qualifies you for that?
只是因为我有感应
I feel things deeply, that's all.
我现在有何感觉？
What am I feeling now?
你想相信没有任何事能影响你
You wanna believe that nothing affects you...
你是天不怕 地不怕
that you're not afraid of anything.
但你充满好奇心
But you're curious...
就像我们一样
just like the rest of us.
我是艾斯蒂 来自哈佛大学人类学系
Stephen Arden. Harvard Anthropology Department.
是跨文化行为的专家
Expert at cross-cultural behavior.
我是贝罗娜 是分子生物学家
Laura Baker. Hi. Molecular biologist.
你是谁？你从事什么工作？
And who are you, and what do you do?
我是连皮斯
Preston Lennox.
我来了这里
And if I'm here...
证明有灾难发生了
the shit has hit the fan.
你的专长究竟是什么？
What exactly is your area of specialty, Mr. Lennox?
专责为政府解决问题
I'm a freelance solution to our government's problems.
什么问题？
What exactly might they be?
人们不想提起的问题
The kind people don't usually like to talk about.
你狩猎人 对吗？
You hunt people, don't you?
是的
I guess so.
你在房内吗？现在看电视太夜了
You in here? It's a little late for TV.
你在吗？
You in here, honey?
晚安 我是费舒
Good evening, I'm Xavier Fitch.
这次行动的主管
I'm in charge of this operation.
你们可以坐近一点吗？
Would you sit a little closer, please?
1974年11月
In November of 1974...
S.E.T.I.的一个小组…
a small group from S.E.T. I...
S.E.T.I.即是探索地外生命计划
S-E-T-I, Search for Extraterrestrial Intelligence...
他们在阿雷西柏利用无线电碟形天线…
used radio dishes at Arecibo...
向所有在听着的人发放信息
to send a message to whoever was listening.
他们传送了250个位元组的资料
They sent a quarter of a kilobyte...
包括人类的DNA结构…
including structure of human DNA...
我们太阳系的地图
a map of our solar system...
地球的人口 还有其他有用的资料
population of the Earth. Helpful facts like that.
1993年1月 阿雷西伯收到回复
In January of 1993, Arecibo received a message back...
是由外星人发出的
from an extra terrestrial...
来历不明
unknown source.
真厉害
That's great.
地球以外的智慧生命体？
Intelligent life beyond this planet?
对
Yes.
共有两则回复
There were two communications.
第一则是沼气的强力催化剂
The first message turned out to be a superior catalyst for methane.
我们现在有能力
We now have the potential...
用沼气提炼出无限能源
to produce infinite energy from this clean-burning fuel.
因此我们相信他们是友善的
This convinced us we were dealing with a friendly intelligence.
第二则是DNA的新排序
The second message turned out to be a new sequence of DNA...
还有充足的指示使我们能重新组合DNA
with friendly instructions on how to combine it with ours.
那些是技术数据 有问题便问贝博士
Here's some technical data. Get feedback from Dr. Baker.
基本上
Basically...
我们把新的DNA排序
the new combined DNA sequence...
注入一百个
was injected into 100...
人类的卵子
human ova.
有七个…
We got 7...
产生分裂
to divide.
四个逐渐停止了
Four petered out.
两个储存在液态氮中
Two were stored in liquid nitrogen.
我们让一个继续生长
And we allowed one to grow.
它的代名是『西儿』
Its code name is "Sil."
两小时后是这样
That's after 2 hours.
一日后
One day.
两日后
Two days.
- 天啊 - 它的生长速度很惊人
- My God. - This growth is amazing.
一星期后
A week.
- 是个女孩 - 是的
- It's a girl. - Yes.
我们决定制造女孩 因为她较易驾驭
We decided to make it female so it would be more docile...
- 较易控制 - 驾驭和控制？
- and controllable. - More docile and controllable, huh?
出去走走
Well, I guess you guys don't get out much.
那是她出生后一个月
That's her 1 month after she was born.
你把她关在那里？
So you kept her caged in there?
把她隔离比较安全
It was safer to keep her isolated.
她不喜欢这样
She didn't like being locked up.
她不喜欢单独一人
She didn't like being alone.
对吗？
Didn't she?
她在隐藏身体里的一些东西
She's hiding something. Something inside.
对
You're right, Dan.
这是她出生后三个月 看清楚
This is three months after she was born. Watch carefully.
那是什么？
What the hell was that?
倒带看看
Back the tape up.
看她的眼睛
Watch her eyes.
眼睛迅速移动 她在做梦
Rapid eye movement. She's dreaming.
- 是恐怖的噩梦 - 是焦虑不安的反应
- She's having horrible nightmares. - It's some kind of anxiety reaction.
这也令我不安
Got me a little anxious.
还令研究队伍有点不安
It made the research team a little anxious too...
因此我们决定终止实验
so the decision was made to terminate the experiment...
先研究我们在应付些什么
to run more research to see what we were dealing with.
你们打算用毒气杀死她？
You were going to gas her?
我们已经决定了
That was the decision.
这令你很难过
It makes you feel mad.
要杀死她你很难过 对吗？
You feel mad that you had to kill her, don't you?
我不知道
I don't know.
好
Yes.
昨天在盐湖城的火车上发现一个露宿者的尸体
Yesterday the body of a transient was found in a boxcar near Salt Lake City.
初步的DNA测试发现
Preliminary DNA tests conclude...
他是被我们所创造的西儿所杀
he was killed by our creation, by our Sil.
有发现其他尸体吗？
Found any other bodies?
- 暂时未有 - 你会的
- Not yet. - You will.
她是捕猎者
She's a predator.
她的眼睛在前方
Her eyes are in front...
所以她能辨别与猎物的距离
so she can judge the distance to her prey.
对
That's right.
你在哪里学的？
Where'd you learn that?
我看电视的探索频道
I saw it on the Discovery Channel.
我看过那电视节目
I caught that show myself.
- 伦诺克斯 先生 - 嗯？
- Mr. Lennox. - Yeah?
作为…
As the...
非科学家 你清楚事情的始末吗？
non-scientist amongst us, are you clear about what's going on?
清楚
I think so.
你们取得外太空的方程式
You created a monster...
创造了一头怪物
with a formula you got from outer space.
她逃走了 你想我们找寻和杀了她
The damn thing got away. Now you want us to hunt it down and kill it.
接近吗？
Now, is that pretty close?
是的
I guess.
你不想我们…
You don't want us...
活捉她作为研究之用吗？
to capture her alive so that we can study her?
这绝对是寻找和毁灭的行动
Laura, I think this is strictly a search and destroy operation.
向我求助的人都想消灭他们的目标
Nobody ever asked me to find anything they didn't want dead.
我很遗撼
I'm sorry for you.
那么…
Yeah, well...
谢谢
Thank you, Dan.
我为她感到遗撼
I'm sorry for her.
请注意
May I have your attention, please?
欢迎来到洛杉矶 这是沙漠之星的终点站
Welcome to Los Angeles. This is the terminal stop for the Desert Star.
请各位乘客下车
All passengers please disembark.
洛杉矶
有些坏事发生了
Something bad happened here.
- 没错 - 她的颈被压碎了
- No shit. - Crushed her larynx.
她很害怕
She was afraid.
很惶恐 惊慌
She's scared, frightened.
还很饥饿 她饥不择食
Hungry too. She's been eating like a horse.
她肯定没有节食
Our girl is definitely not on a diet.
她为某些原因储存能量
She's storing calories for something.
有头绪吗？
Any ideas?
我的…
Oh, my...
哇 那是
Well, that's...
它看来像…
That looks like some sort of...
蛹 或是卵囊
chrysalis. Some kind of cocoon.
我们在找巨型蚕虫吗？
What are we looking for, a giant moth?
若那是卵囊
If that is a cocoon...
她现在已经完全成长了
she'll be fully-grown now.
她可能因此逃脱了
Maybe that's how she got by our people.
因为我们的人在找小孩
They were looking for a child.
她是小孩
She is a child.
这里很臭 我到外面去
It stinks in here. I'm going outside.
快找那售票员的身份证和信用卡的号码
Get the conductors' ID and credit card numbers on your computer.
这些东西都不在列车上
There's no sign of them on the train.
- 假设她拿走了吧 - 我会安排的了
- Let's assume she took them. - I'll see to that.
受威胁时她会杀人
She kills if she's threatened.
她没有半点自责
And she has no remorse about it. None.
洛杉矶最适合她
Of course, Los Angeles is perfect for her.
这是充满未来的城市
It's a city of the future.
什么事物都可行
Anything goes.
人口不断流动 每个人都是陌生人
Totally mobile population. Everyone's a stranger.
没有什么忌讳 没有什么不能够接受
Very little is taboo or unacceptable.
她做什么都没有人留意
Whatever she does, no one will notice her.
任何事情都是 所以…
Well, whatever. So...
洛杉矶是我们战斗
Los Angeles is where the battle will be fought...
和获胜的地方
and won.
你很漂亮
You look very pretty.
你有百元钞票吗？
Do you have a hundred?
有了
Here we are.
小心看管你的钱 不是所有人都像我那么诚实
Be more careful with your money. Not everybody's as honest as me.
你由外地来的吗？
Are you foreign?
你会说英语吗？
Do you speak English?
- 会 - 拿着
- Yes. - Here. You keep this.
让我拿这个
Here, let me take this.
保重
Be careful here.
好
Yes.
小心
Watch your step.
我们的实验室访客基地一号…
Our laboratory, Visitor Base One...
正搬到大学现在没用的病毒研究实验室
is being moved to some empty virus research labs at the university.
他们在搬运仪器 八时便能开始运作
They're moving our equipment now. It'll be operational by 8:00.
你们去登记房间 十五分种后在这里集合
Check into your rooms. Everyone out front in 15 minutes. We'll go over.
我们要做什么？
What will we do?
研究火车上的证据
Process the evidence from the train.
我们能用那生物的DNA繁殖他吗？
Could we try growing this creature with its own DNA?
我们制造一个不含人类DNA的样本 研究他的弱点
We do a version without ours this time and investigate its vulnerabilities.
这提议很好
That'd be good.
- 我也想知道他的弱点 - 合情合理
- Then I could know how it feels. - Makes sense.
他的人类身体可能只是掩饰
This human life form could be a mask. Without the camouflage...
对 至少我们会知道在对付什么
You're right. At least we'd know what we were dealing with.
沙哈兰汽车酒店
几个笨蛋刚走了 我有客人
A couple of bozos just ran out. I got a customer.
- 有什么可以帮你？- 我想要一间房间
- Yes, young lady. Can I help you? - I want a room.
加上税后 六十二元 这是密月套房的价钱
62, including tax. That'll just about cover the Honeymoon Suite.
你好 你经常来的吗？
Hi. Come here often?
你的星座是什么？
What's your sign?
厌倦了黑发吗？
Tired of brunette?
改变吧
Change.
改变头发的颜色
Change the color of your hair.
『头发色素』
Color-Tress.
我放大倍数了
I've increased the magnification.
我注入细胞后就会形成外星DNA
When I pierce the cell, the foreign DNA will be introduced.
可恶
Shit!
摄影机坏了
The camera's gone down.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你们有后备的吗？
Do you have a replacement camera?
有 但更换需要一点时间
We do, but it'll take time for the technician to replace it.
我的实验室经常发生这种事 很简单
No. This happens in my lab all the time. It's simple to replace it.
你能做到吗？
You saying you can do it?
当然 但我需要别人帮忙
Sure I can. I just need somebody to give me a hand.
技术人员不能入内 这项计划是保密的
I don't want technicians in there. This is classified.
我来帮忙
I'll do it.
- 行动派的人 我喜欢 - 那就是我
- Man of action, I like that. - That's me.
你能帮我除掉那颗吗？
Can you get that one for me?
把摄影机给我
Give me the camera.
有点不对劲
Something's... Something's wrong.
天啊 他已经开始了
Christ, It's started already.
- 快把它盖上 - 什么
- It's started. Get the top back on. - What?
快把它盖上
Laura, Press, get the top back on.
这样就对了
Here you go.
她注入了细胞
She must have penetrated the cell.
- 可恶 - 那是什么？
- Shit. - What was that?
他掉了螺栓
He dropped the bolt.
- 快找那螺栓 快把它盖上 - 我正在找
- Find the bolt. Get the top on. - I'm looking, Fitch.
他们听到吗？
Can they hear me in there?
罗娜 皮斯
Laura, Press...
- 把它盖上我便让你们出来 - 它们掉到哪里？
- get the top on, then I'll let you out. - Where'd it go?
- 它掉进铁丝网里 - 你能拿起它吗？
- It fell through the grate. - Can you lift it up?
- 我拿不开它 - 不能拿开它
- It's not gonna move. - This isn't going anywhere.
- 我拿不到它 - 皮斯
- No, can't get it! - Press...
快找那螺栓
you gotta get the bolt!
- 我不能移动那铁丝网 它被焊接了 - 我的天啦
- Can't get it. The floor's welded down. - Oh, my God.
皮斯 我的天啦
Press. Oh, my God.
- 我从未见过这种东西 - 天啦
- I've never seen anything like this. - Holy shit.
我不能让他们出来
I can't let them out.
- 看 - 来吧
- Press, look. - Come on.
让他们出来
Fitch, let us out of here!
快开门
Open the goddamn door!
- 我要知道里面的是什么 - 快开门
- Not until I know what's in there! - Open it now!
- 让他们出来 - 不可以
- Let them out. - I can't!
- 快开门 - 让我们出来
- Open up the fucking door! - Let us out!
- 告诉我 他会停止生长 - 他不会 快让他们出来
- Tell me it'll stop growing, Dan. - It's not, let them out!
开门
Open up the door!
皮斯 皮斯
Press, Press.
那究竟是什么？
What the fuck is that?!
到另外的门
Laura, get to the other door!
- 让她出去 - 不可以
- Let her out, Fitch! - I can't!
- Let her out! - I can't!
- 混蛋 - 让她出去
- You motherfucker! - Let her out!
- 你让她出去 - 我不能把他困在里面
- You've gotta let them out! - I can't hold it in!
走吧
Get out of the way!
我要烧毁实验室
I'm gonna burn it! Out of the way!
- 这是什么？- 两分种后我要烧掉实验室
- What is this thing? - In 2 minutes, I'm burning the room!
我一定要这样做
I have to do it!
两分种内杀死他
You have two minutes to kill it.
截断气喉用来做喷火器
Disconnect the gas line. Use it as a flamethrower.
罗娜 小心
Laura, watch out!
- 哪里去了？- 那些管子那里
- Where'd it go? - In the pipes!
- 快开门 - 闭嘴
- Open the door! - Shut up, Dan!
余下一分种
One minute remaining.
罗娜
Laura...
他停下来了 我杀死了他
it stopped moving. I think I killed it.
他死了 快开门
It's dead! Open the door!
让他们出来
It's dead, Fitch. Let them out.
天啊 他还未死
Oh, God, it's not dead.
- 见鬼 - 我们该做什么？
- Shit. - What'll we do?
三十秒
30 seconds remaining.
- 没时间了 走吧 - 把门打开
- There's not much time. Let's go. - Open the door!
- 让他们出来 - 我不能这么做
- Let them out. - I can't do that.
- 我得遵守规则 - 什么规则？
- I have to follow protocol! - What protocol?!
做这个实验的规则
The protocols by which we're doing this!
你没有对他们说过
You didn't tell them that before they went in.
- 让他们出来 - 12 11 10…
- Fitch, let them out. - Twelve, 11, 10...
- 让他们出来 - 我得遵守规则
- Fitch, let them out! - I must follow protocol.
让他们出来
Let them out, Fitch!
快 快离开
Go. Get out of there!
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
- 我没有其他选择 - 好
- I had no choice. - Yeah, sure.
规则是要发生问题时烧掉一切
The protocol is to burn the room if anything went wrong!
我在哪里可以找到男人？
Where's a good place to find a man?
在转角一间叫艾特的夜总会
There's plenty of guys at the Id around the corner. It's a club.
你一定会找到男人
You won't have trouble meeting somebody there.
谢谢
Thank you.
你一定会找到的 有人排队的地方便是了
You can't miss it. Look for the long line.
我想要你的信用卡
I need your credit card...
用来付房间杂费 长途电话费等
for room incidentals, long distance calls and so forth.
信用卡？让我刷刷
Credit card? Zip zap?
像运通 诸如此类
American Express, Visa, MasterCard?
就是它了 谢谢 行了
There you go. Thanks. All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
等等
Wait a minute!
你不会想它落入坏人的手上
You don't want this falling into the wrong hands.
不
No.
这是柯士甸 他突破防守 但被龙门接到了
Here's Justin Crawl. It's through and it's covered by the goalie.
什么
Yeah?
有人使用那售票员的信用卡
The conductor's credit card turned up...
在好莱坞 货车已经预备好
in a Hollywood motel. The van's out front.
走吧
Let's go.
你们俩
You two.
好好享受
Enjoy yourselves.
长腿姐姐 你进去吧 来吧
You, legs. You're in. Go on.
你由哪里来？
Where are you from?
- 外地 - 什么？
- I'm foreign. - You're what?
- 我由外地来的 - 真的吗？
- I'm foreign. - Really?
放松
Easy, easy.
我要去一个派对 但没有人送我去
I've got a party to go to and no one to take me.
我会
I'll take you.
- 你会？- 是的
- You will? - Yeah.
我要去洗手间
Okay. I'm going to the little girls' room.
在这里等我
Wait right here.
我很快回来
I'll be right back.
我在这里等你
I'll be right here.
不择手段 对吗？
Whatever it takes, right?
爱与战争中人人平等
All's fair in love and war.
不是很清楚
Can't see much on that.
拿录影带到实验室弄清楚
Get this tape to the lab. Enhance it.
看我们能否看到她
See if we can get a better look.
她很漂亮
She looks nice.
你知道她到哪里去了吗？
Do you have any idea where she went?
- 我会找到她 - 她想找男人
- I'll find her. - She wanted to meet a man.
我提议她到转角的艾特夜总会
I suggested a club called the Id around the corner.
拿走那录影带
Get the tape.
我要去派对 但没有人送我
I've got a party to go to and no one to take me.
在哪里？
Where is this party?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不能在这里停车
Whoa, you can't park there!
快退出去
Back that out!
- 你不能进去 - 发生什么事？
- No, you can't go in there. - What's going on?!
- 有谋杀案 - 所有人都不准离开
- There's been a murder! - No one leaves here! I mean, nobody!
镇上总是有各种行动的
There's always some action in this part of town.
蓝眼的金发女郎
Blue-eyed blonde.
穿黑色长裤 粉红色毛衣 身高五尺十寸 她和谁离开？
Black leggings, pink sweater, 5' 10" tall. Who'd she leave with?
金发女郎和男人一起并非大新闻
Blonde leaves with a guy is hardly news around here.
说出最流行的人 不要说出没出息的人
Name the top attractions. No losers.
他是帮助她
Assume he's socially adept. He'll be helping her out.
是个友善的人 不是浑蛋
A friendly guy, not an asshole.
我在想了
I'm thinking.
- 罗比和一名金发女郎离开 - 是他了
- Robbie left with a blonde. - That's him.
是他了
That's him.
让你看看我的家
Come on. Let me show you the rest of the house.
我还在出汉
I'm still sweaty from that place.
那里太挤迫了
It's so crowded.
喜欢吗？
Like it?
喜欢
Yes.
我想享受一个花洒浴
I feel like a shower.
你想吗？
You want one?
这样吧
Tell you what.
我会享受花洒浴
I'm taking one.
你稍后也想来一个…
You wanna take one later...
没问题
no problem.
脱下衣服
Take off your clothes.
我想看你
I want to see you.
很好
Very nice.
带我回去
Take me back.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
你知道我们为何来这里
You know why we came here.
我改变主意了
I've changed my mind.
你说不？
All right. You said "no."
我听到了 来吧
It's duly noted. Come here.
我要离开
I wanna go!
太迟了 你不能离开
Too late. You're not leaving! You're not!
- 好吧 - 这就好了
- All right. - That's better.
什么事？杀了一个女孩后又杀了这个男人
What's happening? Kills a girl at the club, kills this guy.
她符合精神变态的定义
I'd say she fits the definition of a psychopath.
没有什么约束她
Nothing inhibits her.
没有道德观或社会结构观念
No moral sense, no social structure.
也没有母爱
She wasn't exactly smothered with a mother's love or taught good manners.
我想知道现在发生何事
I asked what was happening.
他做了什么让她很愤怒
He did something, she was angry.
受威胁或有入侵者时 她会杀人
She'll kill if she's threatened or if anyone gets in her way.
威胁什么？
Of what?
她的生命周期
Her life cycle.
她想寻找配偶
I think she's trying to mate.
进行繁殖
Reproduce.
好的
Okay.
她为何要杀那女孩？
So why did she kill the girl?
性别竞争
Sexual competition.
她的手段很强硬
She's hard on the competition.
她找到了配偶
Now she managed to mate.
看来不是很成功 他还穿着裤子
Doesn't look like a success. He's still got his pants on.
- 她很沮丧 - 谁不是？
- She's frustrated. - Who isn't?
怎么一回事？她已跟他来到这里
What's her problem? She was here with him.
可能她拒绝了他
Maybe she rejected him.
她可能有特别的感觉
She probably has special senses.
老鼠能感觉到配偶有疾病或遗传问题
Rats can sense diseased or genetic damage in their potential mates...
我们可以对他进行测试
so we can test his body...
检查他有没有遗传病或缺撼 让他不能做她的…
for hereditary diseases or defects that would make him a loser...
配偶
essentially.
是针筒
Needles.
他可能是瘾君子或糖尿病病人
Maybe he was a doper, or a diabetic.
任何一种都是不能接受的 不好意思
Either way would make him unacceptable. Excuse me.
好了
All right.
是胰岛素 他有糖尿病 就是它了
Insulin. Diabetic. There you have it.
她可以离开 为何要杀他？
She could have just walked out. Why kill him?
他惹怒她了
He pissed her off.
有些男人被拒绝后会纠缠不休
Some men, when rejected, get insistent.
- 通缉他的车 - 已经下了命令
- Put an APB out on his car. - We have.
回酒店去 我想检查看看
We'll go back to the motel. I want to check it out.
较易驾驭和控制吗？
More docile and controllable, huh, Fitch?
- 你有什么意见？- 我有什么意见？
- What do you think, Dan? - What do I think?
她现在想单独一人
I think she'd want to be alone now.
那些车在外面 她不会来
She won't come here with all these cars outside.
你认为她懂得回来这里？
You're assuming she could find her way back here.
对
She could.
这是什么？
What is it?
可能是月经的血
Maybe menstrual blood.
若有月经 她便能繁殖
If she's menstruating, she can reproduce.
我知道
Yes, I know.
见鬼
Shit.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
不好意思
Excuse me.
叫救护车 有人有电话吗？
Call a paramedic! Anybody got a phone?
若你沿十号高速公路往西行…
If your commute takes you westbound on the 10 freeway...
行程将要延误一小时
expect an hour delay.
驾车到马利宝会很慢
The drive will be slow to Malibu.
影像没改善很多
The video enhancement is not that great.
你认为她的年龄有多大？二十？二十三？
How old do you think she is? Twenty, 23?
她应该有发达的繁殖系统了
Her reproductive system should be fully developed.
她的生理时钟速度很快
Her biological clock must be in hyperdrive.
她想生个小孩
She wants a baby.
她有小孩 我们便麻烦了
If she has a child our problems have just begun.
若她生了个男孩 而他的生长速度和她一样…
If her offspring is male and develops at the same rate as Sil...
六个月后能繁殖
it could reproduce in 6 months.
天晓得他会令多少个女人怀孕
God knows how many females it could impregnate.
费奇
Fitch.
一种侵略性的生物
When a predatory species is introduced...
引入封闭性的生态系统…
into a closed ecological system...
较弱的生物会绝种
the extinction of the weaker species is inevitable.
他们在圣达蒙尼加找到那辆没有汽油的宝马汽车
They found the murdered guy's BMW, out of gas in Santa Monica.
她的名字是什么？
What's her name?
- 我不知道 - 你是谁？
- I don't know. - Who are you?
她没有身份证 我只是想知道她有没有事
She didn't have any ID. I thought I'd make sure she was okay.
她有医疗保险吗？
You think she's got insurance?
我不知道 暂时用我的信用卡付款吧
I don't know. Just put it on my credit card for now.
你根本不知道她是谁 你这种好人很少有
And you don't know her name. Guys like you are hard to find.
快拿去实验室化验
Get a lab workup on that, stat.
带她去照X光 要照这里
Get her up to x-ray. I want an x-ray on this.
看来她的肩胛骨折断了
It looks like a scapula fracture.
你的肩膀
Your shoulder wound.
什么事？
What's going on here?
我们需要你帮忙 有一名烧伤病人
Doctor, we need you now. A child burn victim just came in.
- 这里发生什么事？- 医生
- What is going on here? - Doctor, please.
天啊 你看到她的肩膀吗？
Jesus Christ! Did you see her shoulder?
我们现在需要你
Please. We need you immediately.
你没事
You're okay.
我没事
I'm okay.
我肯定你刚才受了重伤
I was sure you were seriously injured.
我没事
I'm okay.
对 这是奇迹
You are. It's a miracle.
我们可以走了吗？
Can we go?
医生说你可以走了吗？
Did the doctor say you could go?
对
Yes.
我们会派人到那里
We'll send somebody over there. Thanks a lot.
柏德湾医院的医生报称遇到怪事
Doctor over at Parkbay Hospital called in with some weird story.
去看看 只是相隔几英里
We should check it out. It's a few miles away.
罗娜…
Laura...
皮斯 去看看
Press, take a car, check it out.
- 柏德湾医院？- 对 柏德湾
- Parkbay Hospital? - Yeah, Parkbay.
她步行走了
She walked.
她向那边走了
She walked that way...
走了不久
not too long ago.
有些水果和芝士
Got some fruit and cheese.
那是什么？
What is that?
你指那暖水池？
You mean the hot tub?
是暖水池
A hot tub.
我喜欢这个地方
I love this place.
远离交通 生意和人群
It's away from the traffic and business and people.
令你觉得不是身处在洛杉矶
Sometimes it feels like you're not in L.A. Anymore.
这里
Here.
我们永远保留这一该
We'll immortalize the moment.
看着镜头
Look at the camera.
- 她的骨骼重生了 - 是她
- This girl literally reformed her bones. - It's her.
谁给她挂号的？
Who checked her in?
去找找看
I don't know. Let's find out.
她没有保险 他用信用卡为她结帐
She had no insurance so this guy put it on his own credit card.
这是他的档案 尊加利
Here's the file. John F. Carey.
有没有他的驾驶执照或住址？
You don't have a driver's license or home address?
没有 只有他的信用卡档案
No, sir. Just an imprint of his credit card.
把你有的资料列印给我们
Give us a printout of what you've got.
好的
No problem.
吃糖吗？
Some candy?
他住在帕利塞德 这里有他的电话号码
It's in the Palisades and he's got a phone number.
告诉费舒我们往那里去 打电话给尊加利
Tell Fitch where we're headed, and try to get John Carey on the line.
我要接电话
I'd better get the phone.
是电话录音机 要留下口讯吗？
I've got his machine. Should I leave a message?
是的
Yeah.
告诉他 他快要和外星生物交配
Tell him he's about to copulate with a creature from outer space.
- 交配？- 是的
- Copulate, huh? - Yeah.
我喜欢你
I like you.
我知道
I know.
我们在一起不是太快
It's not too soon for us to be together.
不 不是太快
No, it's not too soon.
你不需要这些
You don't need these.
这样有点太快
Hey, hey. That's a little fast.
什么事？
What's the matter?
别紧张
Take it easy.
放松点
Just relax.
还有很多时间
There's plenty of time.
什么事？
What is it?
有人来了
I think someone's at the door.
不要走
Don't go.
求求你 我想生个小孩
Please. I want a baby.
什么？你说什么？
What?! Excuse me?
往旁边看看
Let's go around the side.
外边
Outside.
- 什么事？- 可恶的松鼠
- What happened? - A squirrel! A fucking squirrel!
- 她来过这里 - 对
- She was here. - Yeah, she was.
我想肯定她现在不在
I wanna make sure she's not still here.
我们该检查他有否进行过性行为
Perhaps we should check the body for evidence that they've had sex.
我从前很怕血
I used to be scared at the sight of blood.
现在已经习惯了
Now I guess I'm getting used to it.
没错
Oh, yes.
- 救我 - 什么事？
- Help me, please! - Oh, my God. What's the matter?
我们在客厅找到的
We found this in the living room.
她喜欢他
She liked him.
但并不足够
Well, not enough.
跟录影带一样看不到她的样子
Can't see any more on that than we did on the video monitor.
他没有为她拍摄好的照片
He didn't get a good picture of her.
水中没有精液
There's no evidence of semen in the hot tub water.
可能她带走了
Maybe she took it with.
她可能还未交配
So she probably hasn't managed to mate.
- 我们打扰了她 - 对
- We interrupted her. - Yes, I think we did.
说些有用的资料
Give me something I can use.
你最近有什么感应？
What have you come up with lately, Fitch?
她并不害怕我们
She's not scared of us.
当然
That's for sure.
我们都累了
We're all beat.
回酒店休息吧
We'll go back to the hotel and rest.
明晚…
Tomorrow night...
我们再回到那夜总会
we'll go back to the club.
- 完成一切 - 完成一切
- Stake it out. - Stake it out.
她不是蠢才
She's not stupid.
她不会重复做过的事
She won't repeat herself.
没有原因让她再到那儿 那儿提供了个坏样版
There's no point going there. It provided a poor specimen.
我不肯定
I'm not sure.
她来这里只有两天 她只知道这些
She's been in the city two days. It's what she knows.
我宁可到那夜总会…
I'd rather try the club...
总比坐在指挥中心回想我们差点成功的例子
than sit at the command center reminiscing about how close we got.
她会是很好的生物武器
She would make one excellent biological weapon.
可能有人认为我们是星际的杂草
If someone thought we were some kind of galactic weed that would...
会遍布宇宙
spread through the universe.
你是说…
So what you're saying is that...
她是解药 我们是病菌
she's the cure and we're the disease.
说得好
That's well said.
贝罗娜
"Baker, Laura.
加州斯敏谷 曼达道1735号
1735 Meander Drive, Simi Valley, California."
是你 对吧
That's you, right?
我上次查看时是的
Last time I checked.
在这儿有什么消遣？
What do you do for kicks out there?
怀念你这种人
Pine for guys like you.
我也是这样想
That's what I thought.
有人肚子饿吗？
So anyone hungry?
不 谢谢 我很累 要去睡了
No, thanks. I'm beat. I'm gonna try to get some sleep.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Yeah. Night.
- 我和你去吃东西吧 - 谢谢
- I'll have something to eat with you. - Thanks, Dan.
- 你有试过做噩梦吗？- 是的
- Do you ever have nightmares? - Yes.
请你放开我
Please untie my hands.
- 我不会伤害你 - 我做了噩梦
- I wouldn't hurt you. Please. - I have them.
噩梦告诉我 我是谁
I think they tell me who I am.
你为何这样做？
Why are you doing this to me?
我不知道自己为何在这里
I don't know why I'm here.
我不知道自己是谁 谁派我来这里
I don't know who I am, who sent me.
- 你知道吗？- 不
- Do you? - No!
- 你为何在这里？- 我不知道
- Why do you think you're here? - I don't know.
请你放了我
Please let me go.
Please. Please, let me go.
我不会伤害你
I wouldn't hurt you.
我保证
I promise.
- 我不会伤害你 - 你会的
- I wouldn't hurt you. - Yes, you would.
你还未知道
You just don't know it yet.
我不会
No, I wouldn't!
求求你
Please!
我的手很痛
My hands are hurting me.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊
Oh, my God!
天啊 不要
Oh, my God, no!
不 不
No! No!
危险 高电压
罗娜和皮斯喜欢对方
Laura and Press, they like each other.
但他们没有表现出来
They just don't like to show how they feel.
什么
What?
罗娜和皮斯 喜欢对方
Laura and Press, they like each other.
你说什么都好
Yeah, whatever you say, Dan.
这里烟雾弥漫 我到外面去
Look, it's really smoky in here. I'm gonna go outside, get some air.
我会在货车上躺下休息 简直在浪费时间
Think I'll lie down in the van. Have a rest. This is a complete waste of time.
你觉得我们在浪费时间吗？
Get a feeling you're on a wild goose chase?
是的
Yeah.
不好意思
Excuse me.
拿出去 这是我的垃圾桶
Get out of here. This is my trashcan.
是你
It's you.
嗨
Hey!
她在这里
She's here! Hey!
- 是她吗？- 是她
- Dan. Is that her? - Yeah.
这里
Here.
上车
Get in the van.
Everybody get in the van!
他们往山丘那边去了 我们需要直升机
They're heading into the hills. We'll need the helicopters.
他们往尼古斯峡谷去 在麦可伦那里拦截她
We're going up Nichols Canyon. One of you try to block her at Mulholland.
看那
Watch it!
天啊
Oh, my God!
我们封锁了道路 得告诉新闻界些什么
We blocked the road. We've gotta tell the press something.
你要说什么便说什么 但不能说真相
Tell them what you want, just don't tell them the truth.
我不相信她会在夜总会出现 太简单了
I don't buy her showing up at the club. It's too damn convenient.
看到便要相信 你不相信自己的眼睛吗？
Seeing is believing or don't you trust your eyes?
所有人退后
Get back! Get all these people back!
有点不对劲
Fitch. Fitch. It doesn't feel right.
长官
Sir!
我们在门外发现一只掉下了的拇指
We found a severed thumb in one of the doors that got ripped off.
- 让我看看 - 她可能被大门弄伤
- Let me see that. - She may have caught it in the door.
拿去实验室化验 看看是否她的
Get to the lab, see if it's hers.
- 透过基因可以知道那拇指属谁 - 一切都完了
- It'll be genetically identifiable. - It's all over, everyone.
明天起一切回复原状
Tomorrow you can go back to your lives.
恭喜你们完成工作
Congratulations on a job well done.
就这样？
Just like that, huh, Fitch?
不是这样
I don't think so.
请留下口讯 法兰 我会和你吃晚餐
Leave me a message. And Frank, I'm going to dinner.
我们在哪里见面？再见
Where are we meeting? Bye, sweetie.
侍应生
Waiter.
我们赢了
Well, I guess we won.
- 我们赢了 科学输了 - 这样我们不算赢
- We won, science lost. - I didn't think we'd get her this way.
- 没这么容易 - 你会挂念她吗？
- Not that easy. - You sound like you'll miss her.
会
I guess I will.
我会尊敬她
I think I respected her.
虽然这项工作很讨厌 但我很享受
I know this was a hellish job, but I really enjoyed working with you three.
既然由国家付帐 我们再来喝酒
And since Uncle Sam is buying, let's have another round.
侍应生
Waiter!
我不喝酒
I don't... I don't drink.
今晚你要喝
Don't worry, Dan. Tonight you will.
要跳舞吗？
You wanna dance?
- 谁？我？- 对 你
- Who, me? - Yeah, you.
- 好吧 - 好吧
- All right. - Okay.
我知道你没有妻室 但你在纽约有女朋友吗？
I know you don't have a family. Do you have a girlfriend in New York?
以前有一些 但没维持很久
I guess I've had a few, but they don't hang around very long.
我有太多秘密了
I guess I keep too many secrets.
跟我分享一个
You wanna share one with me?
- 现在？- 是的
- Right now? - Yeah.
我知道你做什么 不会吓倒我
I know what you do, and it doesn't scare me.
- 真的吗？- 当然
- Really? - No.
但吓倒很多人
Well, it does most people.
我不想再也看不到你
I wouldn't wanna never see you again.
- 嗨 - 你是…？
- Hey. - What are you...?
对不起 我认错人了
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I thought you were somebody else.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你没事吧？
You okay?
我以为是西儿 我看到她的金发
I thought it was Sil. I saw the blonde hair.
她死了
She's dead, Press.
那拇指证实是她的
The tests on the thumb proved it was her.
你相信测试 但我不相信
You got your test and I got my gut. I just don't buy it.
只要你感觉她在那里 你便有任务
I think as long as you feel she's out there, you got a mission.
可能你不想工作结束
Maybe you don't want this job to be over.
可能不是 那又怎样？
Well, maybe not. So what?
感谢你与我跳舞
Thanks for the dance.
晚安
Good night.
这是什么？
What do you call this?
这叫长岛冰茶
It's called a Long Island Ice Tea.
里面有红茶的吗？
It's got tea in it?
没有
Nope.
很香 我可以试试吗？
Smells nice, can I try some?
随你喜欢
Help yourself.
对你的男朋友有效吗？
Does it work on your boyfriend?
令他厌恶
Yeah. As a repellent.
这个年龄 他算不错了
I don't know. I think he's in remarkably good shape for a man his age.
一杯长岛冰茶
One Long Island Ice Tea.
我喜欢这种红茶
I like these cups of tea.
- 什么？- 太好了
- What? - That's great.
给我一杯
Hey, give me one of those.
我喜欢这些红茶
I like these cups of tea, man.
我很累 要睡觉了
You guys, I'm tired. I'm gonna go to bed.
那么？
So?
她要睡觉了
She's going to bed.
是的
I guess.
但她还是…
She still...
想再见你
wants to see you though.
我去看看你是否说得对
Maybe I'll go find out if you're right about that.
我最怕地震时在这里
I'd hate to be in here during an earthquake.
嗯
Yeah.
你要到哪一层？
What floor do you want?
十楼 谢谢
Ten, please.
我喜欢你的香水
I like your perfume.
真的吗？
You do?
- 谢谢 - 不好意思 我到了
- Thank you. - Excuse me. I get out here.
晚安
Good night.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
请勿打扰
你想要什么吗？
Did you want something?
- 可能吧 - 可能？
- Maybe. - Maybe?
我来整里房间
Housekeeping.
丹 丹
Dan. Dan.
那两个女孩定是喜欢我们这种不平凡的男人
Those two over there. Bet they like unusual men like us.
女人都认为我很奇怪
Women think I'm strange.
我不舒服
I don't feel well.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
到那里跟她们聊聊
Just go over there and talk to them.
我走了 你也该走了 知道吗？
I have to go. And I think you should leave with me, okay?
我想多留一会
I'm gonna stay for a while, actually.
好的
Okay.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
我来整里房间
Housekeeping.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
我坐在那边想
I was sitting over there, wondering...
这么聪明漂亮的女人为何会没有约会？
what two intelligent, glamorous women were doing without dates.
我是艾斯蒂
My name's Stephen Arden.
在哈佛大学教授人类学
I teach anthropology at Harvard.
- 我以前曾住在波士顿 - 嗯？
- I lived in Boston once. - Yeah?
为期一年
For a year.
- 冷得要命 - 很冷
- Froze my butt off. - It's cold in Boston.
这是标和东尼 我忘了你的名字
This is Bill and Tony. I forget your name.
有趣的袜子
Cute little socks.
站起来
Stand up.
你怎样走进来？
How'd you get in here?
- 我偷了钥匙 - 什么？
- I stole the key. - What?
我在楼下看到你
I saw you downstairs, but you were with all those people.
所以便来等你
So I thought I'd come up and wait.
我通常不会遇上这种事
This kind of thing doesn't usually happen to me.
我想跟你在一起
I just want to be with you.
哦 好
Oh, yes.
安全措施呢？
What about protection?
她在这里
She's here. She's here.
皮斯？
Press?
有人在门外
Someone's at the door.
谁？
Who's there?
皮斯 罗娜
Press, Laura.
我是丹 我想跟你谈谈
It's Dan. I gotta talk to you.
他想怎样？
Christ, what does he want?
- 什么事？- 我有可怕的感觉
- What's the problem, Dan? - I just got this terrible feeling.
我有奇怪的感觉 看到西儿和艾的影像
I get this strange thought, this image of Sil with Arden.
西儿和艾在一起
Sil's next door with Arden, Press.
不 她死了
No, no, no. She's dead, Dan.
我走到他的房间 有人跟他在一起
I went to his room and there's someone in there with him.
- 你有敲门吗？- 有 但我不知道她有何反应
- Did you knock on the door? - Yes, but I don't know what she'll do.
他们很吵 在进行性行为
They're making a lot of noise. They're having sex.
我知道那是西儿
I know it's Sil, I know it!
好的
Okay.
我相信你 等我穿衣服
I believe you. I'll get dressed.
我非常享受
I enjoyed that immensely.
- 我感觉到 - 什么？
- I felt it. - What?
开始了
It's started.
什么？
What's started?
生命
Life.
我亲爱的女孩
Oh, my darling girl.
有些女人相信自己能感觉到受孕
In some cultures, women believe they know the moment of conception...
你不相信？你来感觉吧
Don't you believe me? Feel.
可恶
Holy shit!
希望你是对的
I hope you're right about this, Dan.
- 她往地下室去了 - 我们走楼梯
- She's headed for the basement. - We'll take the stairs.
罗娜 跟我来
Laura, come with me!
来吧
Come on!
若她怀孕了 我们得在她生育前找到她
If she's pregnant, we gotta get to her before she gives birth.
我们不知道那究竟是什么生物
God. We don't know what we're dealing with here.
她可能一次能生十二个小孩或者一千粒卵
She could have a dozen babies. She could lay 1000 eggs!
你看到艾吗？
Oh, God. Did you see Arden?
看到 可怜的蠢才
Yeah, I did, that poor bastard.
我们能抓住她 地下出口的防烟门由里面打开了
We can trap her. The fire door opens from the inside at the bottom exit.
然后怎样？
Then what?
可恶
Holy shit.
- 我的天 - 她穿过钢门逃走了
- Oh, my God. - The bitch went through a steel door!
费舒 丹 我们在停车厂 她避开了我们
Fitch! Dan! We're in the garage! She got past us!
- 你看到她吗？- 我们来到时她已经走了
- You saw her? - She was gone before we got here.
- 这儿 - 你看到她
- Here. - You saw her!
- 看那门 - 她往哪里去了？
- Look at the door! - Which way did she go?
- 皮斯在哪里？- 他到隧道去了
- Where's Press? - He took off down that tunnel.
受威胁时她会杀人
She kills if she feels threatened.
她一定来过这里
She must've come through here.
她进去了 这儿没别的路
She went down here. There's no other way.
对 她进去了
Yeah, she's down there.
走吧
Let's go.
退后 让我清除障碍
Stand back, I'll clear it out.
丹 她到哪里去了？
Which way did she go, Dan?
- 我不知道 - 什么
- I don't know. - What?
我不肯定
I'm not sure. She's here.
想一想 你该有第六感 哪一边？
Think. You're supposed to have some extrasensory power! Which way?
- 她往哪里去了？- 我不知道
- Which way did she go, Dan? - I don't know! I don't know!
- 那边 - 这已经足够了
- I think she went that way. - That's good enough for me.
你认为她到哪边去了？
You think she went that way?
你不是确实知道的 对吧？
You don't fucking know, don't you? You don't fucking know.
我到这边 你跟我来
I'll go this way. You come with me.
- 丹 跟我来 - 费奇
- Come with me, Dan! - Fitch.
她该到了这边
I think she went this way.
丹
Dan?
丹？
费奇 费奇
Fitch. Fitch.
丹
Dan?
什么事？
What happened?
我感应到她
I can feel her.
她在那边
She's that way.
我没想到自己会想杀人
I never thought I'd want to kill something.
从未想过
Never thought I'd want to.
在这边 回到这里
It's this way. It's back here.
她走进去了
Hey, she went in here.
这是地震造成的
This must have opened up during the earthquake.
好 退后
Okay, stand back.
是石油吗？
Is that oil?
看来是
Looks like it.
我回去看看能否赶她出来
I'm going back there to see if I can flush her out.
若她走来这里 便攻击她
If she comes back through here, let her have it.
丹 丹
Dan. Dan!
- 这是什么？- 我不知道
- Dan, what is it? - I don't know.
我不知道
I don't know.
丹
Dan.
好
Okay.
没事的
It's okay.
没有人会伤害你
Nobody's gonna hurt you.
来这里
You come here.
来吧 我扶你
Come on. I got you.
丹出事了
Press, something's happened to Dan!
你没事吧？
You okay?
可恶
Shit!
丹
Dan?
丹？
我被卡住
I'm stuck!
快来帮忙 我被卡住
I need your help! I'm stuck!
支持下去
Dan, you gotta hang on!
皮斯
Press!
丹 坚持住
Dan, keep on.
皮斯
Press!
丹 支持下去
Hang on, Dan!
支持下去
Hang on!
我抓住你了
I got you.
我抓住你了 支持下去
I got you, Dan. Hang on.
可恶
Shit.
坚持住
Hang on!
坚持住 丹
Hang on, Dan!
干掉她
Get rid of her, Press!
低下头
Duck your head.
混蛋 再见
Let go, you motherfucker.
- 我抓住你了 - 见鬼
- I got you. Hold on, I got you. - Shit.
我以为死定了
I thought I was dead.
我以为你喝了最后的长岛冰茶
I thought you'd drank your last Long Island Ice Tea.
彼此彼此
Yeah, I thought we all had.
你没事吧？
Hey, you okay?
我很好
Yeah, I'm okay.
我的裤子一团糟
My pants are a little messed up.
但我没事
But I'm okay.
她一半是人 一半是不知名生物
She was half us, half something else.
我想知道哪一半是捕猎性的一半
I wonder which was the predatory half.
死掉的一半
The dead half.
离开这里吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
我没想过会这么高兴回到污水道
I never thought I'd be so happy to be back in a sewer.